本节目包含暴力场景和粗口内容
The following programme contains strong language and violent scenes.
ed3000 原创翻译出品
你要去塔林 UDC会在那里
You're going to Tallinn. UDC's going to be there.
我会在四天后宣布River项目
I'm announcing River in four days
并将在28号发布
and it will be released on the 28th.
他现在在哪里 他应该在塔林
'Where is he now?' He should be in Tallinn.
你需要找到他并跟着他
You need to find him and stay with him.
目标距离75米
Distance to the target is 75m.
有什么障碍物 一个金属探测器
What are the obstacles? A...metal detector
和一个超敏感扫描仪
and an ultra-sensitive scanner
不过我有办法解决 很聪明
but I've got an idea for that. That's very clever.
玻璃是防弹的
The glass is bullet-resistant.
能挡住7.62毫米步枪的五发子弹
It'll stop five rounds from a 7.62mm rifle.
真是他妈的艺术品
That is a fucking work of art.
你能给他们打个电话吗
Can you call them please?
我不想她在这里 安吉拉 进去
I do not want her here. Angela, go inside.
我在和我丈夫孩子说话 请回屋里去
I'm talking to my husband and child! Please go back inside.
你看起来是个好人
You have good man face.
你为什么需要这个伪装
'Why do you need this disguise?'
有人在找我
'There are people looking for me.'
请出示下证件
Could I see some ID, please?
嗨 是拉斯姆斯吗
Hi, is that Rasmus?
我在想你想不想喝一杯
I just wondered if you wanted to grab a drink?
你觉得我给人什么感觉
What sort of vibe would you say I have?
有点严肃 也有点危险
Kinda serious. Also a bit dangerous.
有些花朵
# Some flowers
永远无法绽放见到阳光
♪ Never get to bloom and see the day
有些花朵
♪ Some flowers
心甘情愿虚度光阴
♪ Are content to wish Their lives away
有些会盛开
♪ Some may rise
有些会凋零
♪ And some may fall
但只有
♪ But only
你能
♪ You may
真正
♪ Ever
看见我
♪ See me true
所以只有
♪ So, only
你能
♪ You can
明白
♪ Tell that
这就是真实的我
♪ This is who I am
♪ This is who I am!
不会说谎
♪ No lie
知道
♪ Know that
这就是真实的我
♪ This is who I am ♪
两名英国情报人员
So, two British Intelligence officers
昨晚从布达佩斯来到这里
arrived here last night from Budapest.
男性 三十多岁 白人
Male, mid-30s, white,
身高约5英尺10寸 棕色头发
about 5'10", brown hair.
女性年龄相仿
Female about the same age,
黑人 名字叫比安卡
Black, first name: Bianca.
我在想你的人能否对付他们
I was wondering if your people might be able to do something about them.
等等 你是在寻求我的帮助吗
Wait, are you asking me for my help?
没错
Sure.
我明白了 罗丁周五到达
On it. Rodin's arriving on Friday.
他们会问我你是否有把握完成
They're gonna ask me if you're confident it can be done.
你想让他们听什么就告诉他们什么
Well, you can tell them whatever they wanna hear.
这也是我个人想知道的
Well, I'm also asking for myself.
那你想让我告诉你什么
So, what would you like me to tell you?
你能搞定
That you'll deliver.
我是站在你这边的
I'm on your side.
我希望这一点现在已经很清楚了
I was hoping that would be clear by now.
我希望我们能更深入地合作
I was hoping this could be even more of a collaboration.
我不搞合作
I don't collaborate.
在完成之前你不会听到我的消息
You won't hear from me until after it's done
我希望能及时收到报酬
and I expect to be paid promptly.
是我
It's me.
是的 我需要现场优先协助
Yeah, I need some priority assistance on site.
好的 我马上把详细信息发给你
Sure, I'll have the details sent to you right away.
我们已经在文化专员办公室为你安排好了
We've set you up in the Cultural Attache's office.
早上好 欢迎加入阿努比斯行动
Good morning. Welcome to Operation Anubis.
看来有人终于行动起来了
Someone's pulled their finger out.
外交大臣并不是特别慷慨的人
The Foreign Secretary isn't a particularly generous man.
但他对豺狼杀害他的朋友曼弗雷德
But he's personally very miffed about the Jackal
感到非常愤怒
killing his friend, Manfred.
他的DNA和指纹有匹配结果吗
Did we get any matches from his DNA and prints?
一无所获
Nothing.
这家伙就像个鬼魂
This guy's a fucking ghost.
爱沙尼亚内部安全局的奥斯卡·伊尔维斯是我们的联络人
Oskar Ilves of the Estonian Internal Security Service is our liaison.
他的团队正在搜查酒店 旅馆
His team is going through hotels, hostels,
爱彼迎和私人出租房
Airbnb's and private rentals.
他们还需要一张画像
They're also asking for a likeness,
所以我要你们见见科尔
so I want you to meet Cole.
科尔会帮你们画出豺狼的样子
Cole is going to help you put a face to the Jackal.
再宽点
Wider...
对 就是这样 没错 就这样
It's a bit more, yeah... just like that. Yep. Like that.
别动了 好 你觉得怎么样
Don't do anything else- Right, OK, yeah. What do you think?
文斯 你见过他 对吧
Vince. You saw him, right?
只看了一瞬间 你觉得呢
Oh. For a split second. Well, what do you think?
呃 对 可能是他
Uh... Yeah, yeah. Could be him.
听着 奥西 这是最好的效果了
Look, Osi, this is the best it's gonna get it.
好吧
OK.
我们会把画像交给奥斯卡和爱沙尼亚人
We'll share it with Oskar Ilves and the Estonians.
谢谢你 科尔
Thank you, Cole.
先生 我刚得到消息 英国队伍在匈牙利
Sir, I've just heard a British team tracked
追踪到那个杀手
the assassin to Hungary.
可惜他逃走了 他很狡猾也很危险
Unfortunately, he got away. He's resourceful and dangerous.
你不能去塔林 就在这里发布
You cannot go to Tallinn. Do the launch from here.
如果我躲起来
If I hide away...
River的敌人就赢了
River's enemies win.
我们筹划这件事已经一年了
We've been planning this for a year.
来宾都已邀请好了 一千人
The guests have been invited, 1,000 of them.
都是随机选择的普通人
Ordinary people, all randomly selected.
他们到达之前都不知道要去哪里
They have no idea where they're going until they get there,
而且都签了保密协议 人们会议论的
and they've all signed NDAs. People talk.
如果现在取消 UDC会很难看
If we cancel now, UDC looks ridiculous.
难看总比死了好
Better ridiculous than dead.
这还不一定
Debatable.
早上好 你在这啊
Morning. There you are.
抱歉 我一早有事 不想吵醒你
Sorry, I had something early and I didn't wanna wake you.
那是什么 哦
What's that? Oh.
我弄到了康斯特迪萨厅的这些图纸
I managed to get my hands on these plans for the Konsterdisaal.
这些人的成就真是令人惊叹
It's pretty astonishing what these guys managed to achieved.
是啊 我觉得昨晚也很棒
Yeah, I thought last night was pretty great too.
你笑起来很好看 拉斯姆斯
You've got a very nice smile, Rasmus.
谢谢 你散发着一种善意
Thank you. No, you sort of radiate kindness.
哇 这是件好事
Wow. No, that's a good thing.
现在这年头善意可是稀缺品
You can't have too much kindness these days. Hm.
呃 如果你想比拼的话 我得告诉你
Uh... if you're trying to compete, I should let you know
没什么比蓝图更让我兴奋的了
that nothing turns me on like a blueprint, so... Hm?
给我看看精彩的部分
Show me the hot bits.
你想知道吗 想
You wanna know? Yeah.
真的吗 对
Yeah? Yeah.
这里
So that bit there...
亲爱的 你好
最近怎么样 我很好
但是... 真的好吗
嗯 我没事
对 我没事
还是在假装没事
这我也不太确定
你相信他说的话吗
现在我只能选择相信
努里
Nuri...
你弟弟有事想问你
你是怎么看出来的
And how could you tell?
大概要上去看看才知道
U...Probably by getting up there and having a look.
但这根本没解释清楚
But this isn't even trying to explain it, so...
我可以带你去
Well, I could take you.
看看
Have a look.
真的吗 嗯
Really? Mm.
不过得今天下午去
It would have to be this afternoon, though.
今晚有演出 整个场地都会封锁
There's a concert tonight and they'll shut the whole place down.
完全封闭 这是怎么回事
Like, total lockdown. What's that about?
我不知道 他们只是告诉我们今晚之后
I dunno, they just told us that after tonight
没有特别许可谁都不能进出
no-one's getting in or out without special permission.
他们让我今晚就走
Well, they've got me leaving this evening now, so,
所以如果可以的话我能下午去
I could do this afternoon, if that works?
你能让这趟值得吗
Would you make it worth my while?
你知道里面有多少钱吗
不知道 也不想知道
让我告诉你
你父亲在世的时候
我总是清楚他有多少钱 分毫不差
这才叫婚姻
我问这个是因为对我很重要 是个不想错过的机会
还记得我朋友安东尼奥吗 就是市中心开酒吧那个
他想转让酒吧 不是全部 只是一半
他想让我买下来
我必须在周五前筹到钱 否则他就会卖给第一个愿意买的人
要四万块
这可是加的斯市中心的酒吧
这会改变你弟弟的人生
你自己决定吧
谢谢 让开
亲爱的 别担心
你是在给他一个机会
帮助他人最是美好
不用说我也知道
这让我很开心
我为你感到骄傲
你真是不要脸
一切都还好吗
Everything OK?
嗯 还好
Yeah.
我们都很好
We're all good. Hm.
四万块
我一定会还查尔斯每一分钱的
让开
大家好
嘿 拉斯姆斯
Hey, Rasmus!
还好今晚不用值班
Fuck, I'm glad I'm not working tonight.
想象一下要坐三个小时听古典钢琴
Imagine having to sit through three hours of classical piano.
真是难以想象
Imagine.
那么 我就在这等你了
So, um... I'll just wait for you.
用这个进来就行 随意点
Use this to get back in here. Knock yourself out.
拉斯姆斯
Rasmus?
嘿 感觉如何 你根本不知道刚才演奏的是什么
Hey, how was that? You have no idea what that was.
那真是太精彩了
That was, uh... that was pretty extraordinary.
什么
What?
不 你看起来特别开心 真有意思
No, you're just so happy about it. It's hilarious.
对我来说 这真的是件大事
That, for me, that was... that was a big thing.
对
Right.
谢谢
Thank you.
不用谢
No problem.
要去吃点东西吗
Do you wanna grab some food?
我很想去 但飞机起飞前
I'd love that, but I've got a ton of things I've gotta do
还有很多事要做
before I fly, so...
等我来取东西时再见吧
But I'll see you when I come and pick up my stuff?
好啊 行吗
Sure. Yeah?
嗯 好吗
Yeah. Yeah?
好 好
Yeah. Yeah.
我已经和UDC的安保主管
I've established a line of communication
基思·坎维建立了联系
with Keith Canvey, UDC's head of security.
我已经把画像发给他了
I've sent him the facial composite.
但他基本上什么都不愿透露
But basically he won't share anything with us.
连UDC要来塔林都不承认
He's not even admitting UDC's coming to Tallinn.
奥斯卡·伊尔维斯找你 奥西 开扬声器
I have Oskar Ilves for you, Osi. Put him on speaker.
奥斯卡 你好 我是奥西
Oskar, hi. It's Osi.
嗨 有个警察认出了画像上的人
'Hi. We have a police officer who recognises the facial composite.
昨晚她在一家爱彼迎见过这个人
She talked to the guy last night at an Airbnb.
是个英国人 叫彼得·吉布森 我正在赶往现场
British. Name of Peter Gibson. I'm on my way to the location now.'
奥斯卡 我派一队人过去
Oskar, I'm sending you one of our teams.
肖恩 安排交通工具和武装护卫
Siobhan, get them transports and an armed escort.
理查德和菲尔会护送你们
Your escort is Richard and Phil.
五分钟后在大楼前集合
They'll meet you at the front of the building in five.
我找到爱彼迎的位置了
I've got the Airbnb location.
不 快趴下
No! Down, down!
跟我来 快
On me! Now!
他直接瞄准你 这是暗杀
He aimed straight at you. That was a fucking hit.
你还好吗 嗯
Are you OK? Yeah.
要进来吗
Do you need to come inside?
不 不用 我们得走了
N-No. No, uh... we need to go.
我们得走 走吧 警察的事我来处理
We need to go. Go. I'll deal with the police.
嘿 嘿 嘿
Hey. Hey, hey.
小心点
Be careful.
你没事吧
You OK?
差一点就中弹了
He didn't miss by much.
是啊 蠢货
Yeah... Idiot.
奥斯卡·伊尔维斯 内务安全局
Oskar Ilves, Internal Security.
知道嫌犯在里面吗 还不确定
Do you know if our guy's in there? We don't,
但昨晚他确实在这里
but he was definitely there last night.
所有出口都已封锁 好
We've covered all the exits. OK.
内务安全局 开门
Internal Security. Open the door.
上
Go!
上 上 上 上
Go, go, go, go!
安全 该死
Clear! Oh, shit.
你还好吧 呃 吃了些变质寿司
You OK? Uh... Yeah, I had some dodgy sushi.
希望这些药能让我在飞机起飞前好起来
I'm hoping these'll bung me up before the flight.
信息量太大了
Too much information.
好吧
Right...
这段时间很开心
It's been fun.
不止是开心
It's been more than fun.
拉斯姆斯 你看起来很善良
You got a good-man face, Rasmus.
这是什么意思
What does that mean?
善良好像是你与生俱来的特质
Kindness just seems to come off you naturally.
大概我天性就是个快乐的人吧
Guess I'm just a happy person.
UDC和DagHaus对即将发布的河流项目
'Both UDC and DagHaus have remained tight-lipped
依然守口如瓶
with regards to the upcoming announcement of River.
都柏林 迪拜和吉隆坡
The venues in Dublin, Dubai and Kuala Lumpur
都被传言可能是发布地点
have all been rumoured as possible locations.
UDC已经制造了不小的轰动
UDC has created quite a stir already
暗示其最新发明河流的惊人功能
with hints to what his latest invention, River, can do.'
UDC 保佑他那尖尖的小脑袋
UDC, bless his pointy little head,
还没明白阶级仇恨
hasn't got the memo that class hatred...
现在比以往任何时候
...makes no more sense now,
更没有意义 世界需要团结一致
just when the world needs to pull together, than it ever did.
塔林的行动失败了
It didn't happen. In Tallinn.
是两个俄罗斯人 他们搞砸了
It was a couple of Russians. They botched it.
共产主义结束这么多年 俄罗斯人还是醉醺醺的
Years after Communism, Russians are still drunk,
懒惰 无能 腐败的农民
lazy, inept, corrupt peasants.
民族特性总是能在政权更迭后存活下来
National characteristics always outlive regime change.
时间太紧了 蒂姆
It was very short notice, Tim.
你知道 当罗马人找不到足够的罗马公民
Do you know, when the Romans could no longer find enough Romans
来管理他们的帝国 史上最伟大的帝国
to run their empire, Greatest empire the world has ever known,
他们就开始雇佣外国人
they started hiring foreigners.
结果大家都知道了 衰落和灭亡
The rest is history. Decline and fall.
你明白我的意思吗
Do you understand what I'm saying?
不要用外国人
No foreigners.
嗯
Mmm.
告诉莱诺拉 我们喜欢考夫林的阶级仇恨论调
You tell Leonora we like Coughlin's class hatred line.
这是科赫瓦警官 她确定昨晚看到了你说的人
This is Officer Kohver. She's sure she saw your man last night.
我们在处理这栋楼的入室盗窃案
We were responding to a burglary in the building.
和这层楼的几个租户都谈过
We spoke to a number of tenants on this floor.
其中有一个男人
And one man,
他有些特别 看起来很像这个画像
there was something about him, and he looked a lot like this.
晚上好
Evening.
先生 能让我看看您的包吗
Could I see your bag, sir?
噢 可能是靴子的声音
Oh. It's probably the boot.
谢谢 没问题
Thank you, that's fine.
谢谢
Thank you.
他持有一本名为彼得·吉布森的英国护照
He had a British passport in the name of Peter Gibson.
吉布森怎么付的钱 信用卡
How did Gibson pay? Credit card.
我们正在查看这张卡是否又被使用过
We're checking to see if the card has been used.
我也会让法医小组采集指纹和DNA
I'll also get forensic team in for prints and DNA.
希望能和匈牙利的样本相匹配
Hopefully, we can match results to what we found in Hungary.
让科赫瓦警官和画像师见面
And get Officer Kovher in with the artist.
看能否画得更像
See if we can get a better likeness.
呃 这些我要了
Uh... These please.
再来四包坚果
And I'll get four of the nuts
还有四块巧克力
and... and four of these chocolate bars.
多少钱 三十欧元
How much will that be? Thirty Euros, please.
三十 天哪 三十欧元
Thirty. Thirty Euros, Christ.
谢谢
Thank you.
女士们先生们 请入座
Ladies and gentlemen, please take your seats.
音乐会即将开始
The concert is about to begin.
一切顺利吗
'All good?'
是的 谢谢
Yeah, good, thank you.
所以他们是俄罗斯人
So, they're Russian?
爱沙尼亚人确信是这样 看看这个
The Estonians are convinced they are. Have a look at this.
是啊 有人在想方设法要杀我
Yeah, someone is going out of their way to try and kill me.
行了 我们知道你很重要
OK, we get it, you're a big deal.
好了 我们更新了画像
OK, we've updated the facial composite.
伊尔维斯已经分发给爱沙尼亚所有警察
Ilves is distributing this to every cop in Estonia,
还有机场 港口 火车站
as well as airports, ports, railway stations,
租车公司和会场
car rental offices, and the venue.
你觉得怎么样
What do you think?
豺狼从不会以同一面目出现两次 对吧
Well, the Jackal never looks the same way twice, does he?
伊尔维斯说彼得·吉布森自从付了爱彼迎的钱后
Ilves says Peter Gibson hasn't used his credit card in Tallinn
就再没在塔林用过信用卡
since he paid for the Airbnb.
拉斯姆斯 请从那边走
看看他吃了什么早餐
Let's see what he's had for breakfast.
旧系统明明很好用
The old system was perfectly good.
但它做不到这个
But it couldn't do this.
基思？
Keith?
我是比安卡·普尔曼 这是文斯·派恩
Bianca Pullman. Vince Pyne.
我们是奥西·哈尔克罗的人
We work for Osi Halcrow.
好 来看看我们的目标
Alright. Uh... Meet our guy.
这个多准确？当地一位女警跟他距离
How accurate is this? A local policewoman had eyes on him,
就跟我跟你一样近
as close as I am to you,
观察了一两分钟
for a minute or two.
很好 这对我们很有帮助
OK. It's gonna be very helpful.
还有这个
Yeah. Uh... There's also this.
这是谁？
Who am I looking at?
豺狼伪装后的样子
The Jackal in one of his disguises.
认真的吗？
Seriously?
这个可能帮助不大
Maybe not so helpful, eh?
我看起来怎么样？
How do I look?
所有人18点前必须离开
I want everyone gone by 1800 hours.
从18点起整栋楼实施封锁
From 1800 the entire building is locked down.
没有我的授权任何人不得进出
No-one gets in or out without my personal authorisation.
上层必须完全清空
We'll keep these upper levels empty
只留武装警卫监视观众
with just armed guards up here covering the audience.
基思 给你的搜查犬准备了礼物
Keith, I've got a present for your dogs.
这是豺狼留下的
The Jackal left this behind.
上面可能留有他的气味
Hm. It could have his scent on it.
UDC会在演讲前20分钟到达休息室
UDC will arrive in the green room 20 minutes before the presentation.
已经消过毒了
It's sterile.
灯光熄灭后 瑞玛会做简短介绍
When the lights go out, Rima will make a short introduction.
然后UDC会在防弹玻璃后面发表声明
And UDC will make his announcement behind the bullet-proof glass.
整个媒体团队都在达格豪斯指挥下
The entire media crew's under DagHaus direction.
他们将向所有电视网络提供独家画面
They have the exclusive feed going to all the networks.
值得吗
'Is this worth it?'
总是一个人 卡尔索普先生 是的 总是如此
'Always alone, Mr Calthrop.' 'Always.'
一个人吃饭很可怜
To eat alone is sad.
确实挺可怜的
Yeah, it is pretty sad.
这是什么意思？
Now, what does that mean?
在西班牙我们说 宁缺毋滥
We say in Spain, better alone than in bad company.
对吧？是的
Or no? Yeah.
该死
Fucking hell.
嗨 晚上好 阿尔贝托
- Hey. - Evening, Alberto.
晚上好 卡尔索普先生
Evening. Buenas noches, Mr Calthrop.
叫我查尔斯好吗
Please will you call me Charles?
查尔斯
"Cholls."
查尔斯 查尔斯
Charles. Charles.
对 发音很标准 谢谢
Good, that was perfect! Oh, thank you.
我去给您准备餐桌
Um... I get your table ready.
不 其实我是想
No, it's not actually, I was...
想问你有休息日吗
I was wondering, do you ever get a night off?
有啊 我又不是奴隶
Yes. I'm not a slave.
那个 如果
Well, uh... if...
等你休息时
when you get a night off,
我能否请你跟我共进晚餐
I was wondering if I could persuade you to go to dinner with me?
当然可以
Yes, of course.
各种猜测已经达到沸点
'Speculation's at fever pitch
在爱沙尼亚 大规模安保行动已经
here in Estonia, where a massive security operation is already
在世界著名的塔林音乐厅展开
underway at the world-renowned Tallinna Kontserdisaal...'
所有人数月以来
'Answers to the questions
一直在问的问题
that have been on everyone's lips for months:
到底什么是河流系统 它将如何改变世界
what exactly is River, and how will it change the world?'
全球各地市场和交易所陷入混乱
'Markets and trading floors across the world in chaos.'
对传统金融市场自由的攻击
'...attack on freedoms of the traditional financial markets.'
就像在等待审判日 只有时间能告诉我们答案
'It's like preparing for judgement day.''Only time will tell.'
克里斯
Chris...
我要再检查一遍整栋大楼
I want one last sweep of the entire building.
谢谢 女士
Thank you, ma'am.
啊 瑞玛·巴顿斯
Ah, Rima Buttons.
嗨 天啊 茉莉很喜欢她
Hi! God, Jasmine loves this woman.
是吗 找她合个影吧 我才不要
Yeah? Ask her for a selfie. Oh, I'm not doing that!
嗨 我是瑞玛 你好 很高兴见到你
Hi, I'm Rima. Hello, it's so good to meet you.
来 这边 我带你去休息室
Come. Come this way. I'll take you to the green room.
飞机刚降落 UDC十分钟后到达
Plane just landed. UDC is ten minutes away.
看来他不会取消了
Guess that means he's not cancelling, then.
现在不会回头了
He won't be turning back now.
记住要靠近玻璃 先生
Remember to stay close to the glass, sir.
天啊 是他
Oh, my God, there he is.
瑞玛 嘿 你好吗
Rima! Hey! How are you?
我很好
Oh, I'm good.
谢谢你愿意主持
Thank you for doing this.
开玩笑 这是我的荣幸
Are you kidding? It's an honour!
要是河流系统能让我知道我前夫
If only River would show me how my ex is spending
每月怎么花掉我给他四万美元的赡养费
the forty thousand dollars a month I pay him in alimony,
那个混蛋
the motherfucker.
抱歉 我在抱怨我前夫 而你
Sorry, I'm bitching about my ex, and you...
你在拯救世界
you're saving the world.
谢谢
Thank you.
♪ 兹比格涅夫·普雷斯纳：欧洲统一之歌 ♪
♪ ZBIGNIEW PREISNER: Song For The Unification Of Europe ♪
开始了
Here we go.
谢谢
Thank you.
靠近玻璃
Stay close to the glass.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
让我们欢迎今晚的主持人
please welcome your host for this evening,
活动家 讽刺作家
the activist, satirist
和挑战者 瑞玛·巴顿斯
and provocateur, Rima Buttons.
瑞玛 嘿
Rima! Hey!
我面前的是这个星球上最幸运的人群 对吧
Am I looking at the luckiest people on the planet, or what?
不仅最聪明
Not only the most intelligent,
衣着最讲究 还有嗯
the best dressed, and uh...
可能是最帅最美的
possibly even the best looking...
而且绝对是最幸运的
...but definitely the luckiest.
因为你们正在见证历史
Because you are witnessing history,
就在此时此地
right here, right now!
告诉你们一个小秘密
I'll let you in on a little secret.
我们所知的这个世界
The world as we know it...
已经注定毁灭
'..is doomed.'
对 显然我们完蛋了
Yep. Apparently we're doomed.
我听到了 没错 暖场表演
I heard. 'Yeah, I know. The warm up act
应该让你们热情高涨 而不是吓得魂飞魄散
is supposed to warm you up, not scare the shit out of you.
但是拜托 我可是夸奖过你们
But come on, I flattered you.'
她太酷了 我们需要认真谈谈
She's so cool. 'We need to have a serious talk.
我说的是你们 还有全世界数百万
I mean you, and I mean the millions of people watching this
正在手机和电视前观看的人们
on their phones and TVs around the world.'
我们中的一些人
Some of us,
不 是大多数人 都拥有很多东西
no, most of us, have loads of stuff.
我们又不是在排队领救济餐 对吧
Well, we're not exactly lining up at the soup kitchens, are we?
不要为此感到羞愧 但拥有东西
Don't be embarrassed about it. But just because we have stuff,
并不意味着我们没完蛋
doesn't mean we're not fucked.
我们在自欺欺人
We're in denial.
我们一直假装没有坏事
We keep pretending nothing bad
发生 但我们心知肚明
is happening when we know it is.
来 跟我重复
Come on, repeat after me.
我们完蛋了 我们完蛋了
We're fucked! We're fucked!
我们必须改变 我们都知道
We have to change, and we know it.
这种改变必须从金钱开始
And that change has to start with money,
因为金钱就是权力
because money equals power.
权力何时愿意过改变
And when has power ever wanted change?
改变对有权力的人来说就像氪石 他们会
Change is like kryptonite for people with power. They go all...
啊
'Urgh...'
这是谁
Who is this?
她什么都不是
She's nobody.
一百年前 女性要求
'A hundred years ago, women said...
给我们投票权
give us the vote.
当权者说 不行 那会毁了这个世界
Power went, "No, that would be the end of the world.'
救济穷人 不行 你们不能这样做
Feed the poor. No, you can't do that.
穷人永远都会存在
The poor will always be with us!
权力不会轻易放手 永远不会投降
Power won't give up. It will never surrender.
必须用强制手段
It has to be forced.
而这位就是
And here is the man...
能做到这一点的人 女士们 先生们
...to do it. Ladies, gentlemen,
还有在座的所有人
and all of you in between,
我向大家介绍 乌勒
I give you, Ulle...
达格·查尔斯
Dag Charles!
喔
Woo!
耶 耶
Yeah! Yeah!
就像格拉斯顿伯里音乐节的主舞台
That is like the main stage at Glastonbury.
嗯 别这样
Mmm... Stop it.
他们说我们不会成功 但我们做到了
'They said we'd never make it, but we're here!'
塔林
Tallinn!
时机已到
The time is now!
喔
Wooo!
朋友们 感谢你们今晚来到这里
Friends, thank you for joining me here tonight.
我知道你们都远道而来
I know you've all come a long way.
现在我要请你们
I'm gonna ask you now...
走得更远
to come even further.
我希望你们
I want you...
能和我一起踏上征程
'..to come on a journey with me.'
我跟你去
I'll come!
我实话实说
I won't lie to you,
这不会是一段轻松的旅程
the journey will not be an easy one to make.
有些人需要放弃一些东西
For some, it will involve giving up stuff,
正如丽玛所说
like Rima said.
但这必须要做
But it has to be done.
必须要做
It has to be done!
富人
The rich...
变得如此富有
'have become so rich...'
他真让人恶心
He's nauseating.
权贵变得如此强大
'..the powerful have become so powerful,
腐败分子变得如此堕落
the corrupt have become so corrupt.
这些富有 腐败和强大的人
'The rich, corrupt, and powerful...'
夺走了属于大众的东西
...have taken away what belongs to the many...
并把它藏在
...and hidden it
只有少数人能找到的地方
where only a few can find it.
瑞弗会带领你们
And River is gonna lead you
找到那个地方 让你们
to where it is so you can come
拿回属于你们的
and take back what's...
一切
...yours!
去死吧 暴君
Fuck you, you tyrant!
快来
Come on.
有两个枪手 他就在这里
There were two shooters. He's in here somewhere.
封锁所有出口 行动起来
Lock all the exits. Let's go.
刚才是什么情况
What the fuck was that?!
到底发生了什么
What the fuck just happened?!
那混蛋死了吗
Is the motherfucker dead?
把遥控器给我 不要
OK, give me the remote. No!
给我遥控器 把该死的遥控器给我
Gimme the remote. Give me the fucking remote!
保持冷静
请沿着出口标志前进
所有门都是开着的
关上该死的门
Close the fucking doors!
快 关门
Here! Close the doors!
不 我们不会关门
No, we won't close the doors.
彼得
Peter?
嘿 彼得 是你吗
Hey! Peter? Is that you?
彼得
Peter?
嘿
Hey!
彼得
Peter!
嗨 嘿
Hi. Hey.
我以为你走了
I thought you left?
♪ 安德烈·布拉滕 搭配苏珊·桑德佛: 事件之涌 ♪
♪ ANDRE BRATTEN FT. SUSANNE SUNDFOR: Cascade of Events ♪
♪ 要是能够
♪ If only
♪ 要是能够变得简单
♪ If only it was easy
下周四播出新一集
♪ 要是能够变得简单
♪ If only it was easy
♪ 我们在滑翔
♪ We're paragliding
♪ 仍在坠落
♪ Still falling
♪ 柔软的沙子在四处
♪ Soft sand everywhere
♪ 我们在飞翔
♪ We're flying
♪ 仍在坠落
♪ Mmm, still falling
♪ 下降 ♪
♪ Descending ♪
ed3000.cc 原创翻译出品  参与：贾婷、会飞的猪仔  校对：巴萨姆